哈哈哈
哈
哈哎这
怎么是他呢
这个宋义竟然敢辜负小师妹
宋郎哎呀
夫君你这是什么意思呀
我才是你的发妻啊
至于名与桑明德不配位
我今日必要在此休期
拿着小手赶紧滚吧
这
这不可能啊
夫君你答应过我的
你说我白头偕老
永远都不会负我的
你若再继续纠缠
只会让我对你心生厌化
睁开你的眼睛好好看看
现如今
我已经是前途无量的状元郎了
而你呢依旧是那个
每天穿梭在世界街的乡下裁缝
罢了想做我宋逆的妻子
你不配哈哈哈哈
好我不配
这5年来
你娶我心中喜的时候
为什么不说我不配
我供你的一家吃穿
供你读书的时候
你为什么不说我不配
住口
那不过是你一厢情愿罢了
可你为什么
还穿着我为你一针一线缝的衣服
这些年来
你的所有衣服都是我缝的
你怎么能这么说我呢
桑尼啊桑尼
我承认你之前为我付出了很多
但哪都已经过去了
今日我特意穿上这身衣服
就是想告诉你
从今日开始
你我之间便如同这衣服一般
一刀两断
好一个踪影
竟然敢欺负我们小师妹
我今天非要死了他不可
再等等等到四块金陵齐聚
揭发龙魂一笑之前
我们不能贸然行动
是你放心
只要确认好了小师妹的身份
今天欺负他的
有一个算一个
一个都破不了
Hahaha
Ah!
Ha hey this
Why is that him?
This Song Yi actually dared to let down the little junior sister
Song Lang, oops.
Husband, what do you mean?
I'm your first wife
As for the mismatch between the name and Samminder
I have to take a break here today
Take your little hands and get out
This
That's impossible.
Husband, you promised me
You say I'll grow old together
Will never fail me
If you continue to entangle
It just makes me sick of you
Open your eyes and take a good look
Now
I'm already a promising champion
And you are still the one
The country tailor who shuttles through World Street every day
I just want to be my Song Ni's wife
You don't deserve it hahaha
Ok I don't deserve it
These 5 years
When you were happy to marry me
Why don't you say I don't deserve it?
I feed and clothe your family
For you to read
Why don't you say I don't deserve it?
shut up
That's just wishful thinking
But why do you
Still wearing the clothes I sewed for you
Over the years
I sew all your clothes
How can you say that to me?
Sonny, Sonny
I admit that you have sacrificed a lot for me before
But it's all gone
I put on this dress on purpose today
Just wanted to tell you
Start today.
Between you and me is like this dress
Cut in two
Good trace
How dare you bully our little junior sister?
I'm going to kill him today.
Wait until the four golden tombs gather together
Before exposing the dragon soul smile
We cannot act rashly
Don't worry.
As long as you confirm the identity of the little junior sister
Bullied him today
One counts as one
None of them can be broken.